Hitting the
gym won't
improve erectile
function.
In most
cases, erectile
dysfunction is
related to
weak pelvic
floor muscles,
which are
directly responsible
for erectile
function.
So no
matter how
many squats
or lunges
you do
or how
much broccoli
you eat,
it won't
help because
nothing you
do in
your regular
life affects
your pelvic
floor muscles
at all.
The only
proper way
to strengthen
pelvic floor
muscles and
improve erectile
function is
to do
Kegel exercises.
Recent research
proves this
too.
For instance,
in a
study conducted
at Somerset
Newfield Hospital,
men who
followed a
healthy lifestyle
and exercised
regularly saw
no noticeable
improvements.
Meanwhile, the
majority of
men who
did Kegel
exercises and
nothing more
saw significant
improvements in
the strength
and longevity
of their
erections.
Now, the
best way
to do
Kegels is
them with
the Dr.
Kegel app.
It provides
a step-by-step
plan on
how to
exercise correctly.
You can
exercise while
lying on
your couch,
and it
takes just
five minutes
a day
because it's
the easiest
way to
do Kegels.
Yeah, sure,
anyone can
get it.
Just go
to the
Dr. Kegel
website, answer
a few
questions, and
you'll get
your personal
plan.