Here's how
men can
overcome erectile
dysfunction in
five minutes
a day.
One of
the two
key pelvic
floor muscles
that's crucial
for men's
sexual health
is called
the ischiocavernosis
muscle.
It helps
to fill
and properly
maintain blood
in the
male organ,
which is
necessary so
that a
man can
achieve and
maintain an
erection.
And did
you know
that men
can strengthen
this muscle
with Kegel
exercises and
significantly improve
their erection?
Numerous studies
have found
that with
Kegel exercises,
more than
70% of
men achieve
firmer, longer
erections and
can eliminate
ED.
Additionally, trials
show that
Kegel also
improve ejaculation
control and
help men
last longer.
So,
these exercises
are very
easy to
do and
only take
five minutes
a day.
You can
do them
standing, sitting,
or even
lying on
the couch
watching TV.
But the
best way
to do
Kegel is
with an
app, as
it's much
more comfortable
and efficient.
I recommend
trying the
Dr. A
a step-by-step
plan with
clear and
detailed instructions
on how
to exercise
correctly, as
well as
many helpful
tips. 🕓
on men's
sexual health.