The worst
mistake that
men can
make when
trying to
improve their
sexual health
is using
meds and
testosterone boosters
first while
completely ignoring
a much
more effective
alternative.
You see,
while meds
can provide
desirable effects,
they only
last for
a couple
of hours
because, let's
face it,
they're treating
the symptoms,
not the
real issue.
But the
worst part
is that
regular use
can lead
to serious
side effects
like heart
palpitations, muscle
aches, insomnia,
and more.
That's why
research suggests
a safer
and more
effective way
that men
should use
first, called
Kegel exercises.
And if
you think
that Kegels
are something
complicated that
takes a
lot of
time, you're
completely wrong
because they
can take
just five
minutes a
day.
These exercises
are so
simple, you
don't even
have to
lift a
finger.
You can
literally do
them while
lying on
the couch
watching your
favorite TV
show.
And while
some men
find out
about Kegels
on the
internet, they
usually have
no idea
how to
use the
pelvic floor
muscles, how
often to
exercise, or
which exercises
are the
most effective.
Naturally, you
start wondering,
okay, but
how can
I do
Kegels properly?
In my
opinion, the
best way
to do
them is
with an
app because
it can
provide you
with a
proper step-by-step
workout plan
with proven
and effective
exercises.
The biggest
and most
trustworthy one
is the
Dr. Kegel
app, and
this is
the app
that I
personally use
too.