If you
steal this
routine, your
sexual health
and performance
will be
top notch.
In the
morning, while
you're still
in bed,
do Kegel
exercises for
five minutes.
Then at
the end
of the
day, when
you're in
bed and
ready to
sleep, you
also do
Kegel exercises
for five
minutes.
This simple
routine will
give you
the best
sexual health
boost ever.
When you
do this
for about
thirty days,
you strengthen
your pelvic
floor muscles
and improve
blood circulation
in the
groin area.
This makes
erections stronger
and longer
lasting, and
you'll be
able to
last significantly
longer than
you do
now.
This helps
to prevent
erectile dysfunction,
premature ejaculation,
and many
other male
conditions.
It's also
highly beneficial
for your
prostate health.
Basically, this
routine is
like brushing
teeth, but
instead of
your oral
health, you're
taking care
of your
sexual health.
To keep
up with
this routine,
I use
an app
called Dr.
Kegel.
You get
a step-by-step
plan on
how to
exercise correctly,
and it
sends you
reminders to
stay on
track.
Basically, it's
the easiest
way to
do Kegels.
Yeah, you
should try
it.
It's very
cool!