Here's what
happens to
a man's
body when
he starts
doing kegel
exercises.
In the
first twenty-four
hours after
doing Kegels,
you start
to consciously
feel your
pelvic floor
muscles, and
at the
same time
the blood
flow to
your pelvic
area begins
to increase.
In seven
days, increased
blood circulation
is going
to make
you wake
up with
morning wood
more frequently.
Generally, it
will take
less time
to achieve
an erection,
it will
last longer,
and even
stand at
a higher
angle.
In fourteen
days of
doing Kegels,
the control
over your
pelvic floor
muscles becomes
better.
This will
allow you
to suppress
the urge
to ejaculate
and delay
the finish.
Finally, around
day thirty
is when
the majority
of men
see the
most significant
improvements from
doing kegel
exercises.
By this
time, even
men with
ED report
they can
feel their
erections are
as strong
as when
they were
young.
Moreover, men
gain such
control over
the pelvic
floor muscles
that it
allows them
to last
as long
as they
want.
If you
are ready
to try
kegel exercises
but don't
know how
to start,
pay attention
to the
Dr. Kegel
app.
It can
provide you
with a
step-by-step plan
with detailed
instructions on
how to
do everything
correctly, and
it takes
just five
minutes a
day.