This is
probably the
most important
muscle in
a man's
body.
Every man
has a
special muscle
responsible for
erectile function
located at
the base
of the
male organ.
It's called
the Ischiocavernosus.
What's interesting
is that
by doing
Kegel exercises,
men can
strengthen this
muscle and
increase blood
flow to
the groin
area.
This makes
erections more
firm, longer
lasting, and
can even
eliminate ED
completely.
Additionally, trials
show that
Kegels also
improve ejaculation.
For that
reason, Kegels
are regarded
as the
best way
to improve
men's health
naturally.
And for
the long
term, talking
from experience,
it's better
to do
them with
the app.
It's much
more comfortable
and efficient.
The one
that I'd
recommend is
called Dr.
Kegel.
It provides
you with
a step-by-step
plan on
how to
exercise correctly,
and it
takes just
five minutes
a day.
It's very
simple.
Just go
to the
Dr. Kegel
website, take
a short
quiz, and
you'll get
your personal
plan.