There are
three early
signs of
ED that
most men
overlook.
If a
man experiences
difficulty achieving
or maintaining
an erection,
if his
erection is
not as
firm as
it used
to be
when he
was younger,
or if
his morning
erection is
irregular, this
can already
be a
sign of
erectile dysfunction.
For this
reason, it's
recommended to
do Kegel
exercises for
five minutes
a day.
This will
increase blood
flow in
the groin
area and
significantly improve
erectile function.
The best
way to
do Kegels
is to
do them
with an
app called
Dr. Kegel.
It provides
you with
a step-by-step
plan on
how to
exercise correctly.
It keeps
you on
track, and
basically it's
the easiest
way to
do Kegels.
Anyone can
get it.
Just go
to the
Dr. Kegel
website, answer
a few
questions, and
you'll get
your personal
plan.