There are
two special
muscles that
play the
most significant
role in
male sexual
health and
performance: the
Ischiocavernosus and
the Bulbospongiosus.
The Ischiocavernosus
is located
at the
base of
the male
organ, and
this muscle
helps to
fill and
maintain blood
in the
organ so
that a
man can
achieve and
maintain an
erection.
The second
one, the
Bulbospongiosus, stretches
along the
root, and
this muscle
is responsible
for how
long you
can last
because it
controls the
ejaculatory reflex.
The key
point is
that by
doing kegel
exercises, men
can strengthen
these muscles
and significantly
improve their
erections and
endurance, which
is confirmed
by the
latest survey
where 88%
of men
reported improvements.
The effect
is natural
and long-lasting.
One of
the easiest
and most
comfortable ways
to do
Kegels is
with an
app called
Dr. Kegel,
which can
provide a
step-by-step on
how to
exercise correctly;
you can
exercise while
lying on
the couch,
and it
takes just
five minutes
a day.