Let me
give you
a secret.
This is
what every
man wants:
a cheat
code on
how to
have a
strong erection
and last
as long
as you
want.
Basically, what
you need
to do
is perform
Kegel exercises
for five
minutes a
day during
twenty-five days.
It only
takes about
twenty-five days
for men
to see
improvements.
Yet the
only thing
that you
need to
achieve results
is to
do Kegels
correctly and
consistently.
And this
is why
I recommend
trying the
Dr. Kegel
app in
the first
place.
It can
provide a
step-by-step plan
with detailed
instructions on
how to
exercise correctly.
It'll keep
you on
track.
You can
exercise lying
on your
couch.
Basically, it
is the
easiest way
to do
Kegels.
Yeah, sure,
anyone can
get it.
Just go
to the
Dr. Kegel
website, take
a short
quiz, and
you'll get
your personal
plan.