Here's how men can overcome erectile dysfunction in five minutes a day.
One of the two key pelvic floor muscles that's crucial for men's sexual health is called the ischiocavernosis muscle.
It helps to fill and properly maintain blood in the male organ, which is necessary so that a man can achieve and maintain an erection.
And did you know that men can strengthen this muscle with Kegel exercises and significantly improve their erection?
Numerous studies have found that with Kegel exercises, more than 70% of men achieve firmer, longer erections and can eliminate ED.
Additionally, trials show that Kegel also improve ejaculation control and help men last longer. So,
these exercises are very easy to do and only take five minutes a day.
You can do them standing, sitting, or even lying on the couch watching TV.
But the best way to do Kegel is with an app, as it's much more comfortable and efficient.
I recommend trying the Dr. A
Kegel app.
It provides
a step-by-step plan with clear and detailed instructions on how to exercise correctly, as well as many helpful tips. 🕓
on men's sexual health.